Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Research Fellows, 1930-1945; Accession 2019-A-0023
  - Breisacher, Ernest (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Brody, Bernard Stephen (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bullock, Theodore Holmes (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bunting, Henry (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Burket, Lester William (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Burlew, John Swaim (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Burt, Charlotte Pauline (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Busck, August (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Buyse, Adrian (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Calhoun, Robert L. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Carr, Edward (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Chattaway, Mary Margaret (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chen, Tze Tuan (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Chidsey, Jane Louise (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Chitambar, Theodore P. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Cline, Mildred Anne (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Clench, William James (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cloutier, Berince Ann (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cohen, Arthur (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cooper, Gustav Arthur (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Cooper, Leslie Hugh Norman (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Creighton, Martha (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Cross, Ephraim (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Curtis, Jack Markley (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Dann, Margaret (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Davenport, Horace Willard (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Dawson, James Arthur (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Day, Harry Gilbert (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Defrise, D. (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Demorest, Max Harrison (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Denny-Brown, Derck Ernest (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Deuring, Max Frederich (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Dial, David Llewellyn (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Diller, William Frey (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Dillingham, Louise Bulkley (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Dilworth, Robert Palmer (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Dowman, Charles Edward III (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Dribin, Daniel M. (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Driver, Cecil Herbert (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Drouet, Francis (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Dunn, Esther Cloudman (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Dybowski, Mieczyslaw (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Dyen, Theodore (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Einarson, Benedict (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Elias, Maxim Konrad (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Everett, Cornelius Joseph, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Ezban, Selim (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Faucett, Lawrence William (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Faust, Clarence Henry (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Feist, Elisabeth (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Fiesel, Eva (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Focke, Alfred Bosworth (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Fontana, Giovanni (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Fraad, Daniel Joseph, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Francis, Catherine Mills (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - French, Albert N. (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - French, Robert Linton (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Friedman, Robert (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Gibson, James Jerome (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Goldman, Franz (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Grant, Martin Lawrence (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Crew, Kenneth E. (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Gut, Max (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Habicht, Lojo (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Hackman, George Gottlob (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Hahn, E. Adelaide (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Halle, Fannina W. (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Halasi, Albert Bela (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Halperin, Israel (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Halvorsen, Henry Edvard (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Hanna, William Fielding (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Harrold, Charles Frederick (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Harwood, Heber James (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Hennemann, Martin (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Hilzheimer, Klaus (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Hollinshed, William H. (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Holtfreter, Johannes (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Hornung, Philip John (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Horstadius, Sven (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Horton, Richard Greenfield (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Hsiao, Yuan-Ting (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Hubert, Stanislaw L. (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Hudson, Alfred Emmons (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Hudson, Geoffrey Francis (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Humphreys, Lloyd G. (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Hyyppa, Esa (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Israeli, Nathan (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Jackson, Joseph Francis (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Jackson, Kathleen Olive Patricia (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, Theodore Andrew (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jessner, Friedrich (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Guy Burton (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Kellogg, Winthrop N. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Kemal, Ali (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Kertesz, Stephen (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Kessler, Morris (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Kimball, Richard Fuller (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Kirk, Edward Braxton (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Kitchin, Irwin Clark (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Klinghoffer, Kaimen Anselm (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kraeling, C.H. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Kroner, Richard (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kydd, David Mitchell (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Lacheman, Ernest Rene (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - LaFargue, Thomas Edward (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Landauer, Walter (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Lane, Cecil Taverner (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lane, James Russell (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - LeBlond, Charles Philipe (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Leckie, George Gaines (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - LeCompte, Philip Medford (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Leitch, Andrew (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Lenz, Freidrich Walter (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lepore, Michael Joseph (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Lester, John Ashby, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Levitski, Jakob (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Liebow, Averill Abraham (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Liepmann, Klaus (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Lits, Frans Jean Maurice (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Lloyd, Harriet Exline (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - McCarthy, Barbara Philippa (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - McCullough, Warren Sturgis (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - MacLane, Saunders (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - MacNeille, Holbrook Mann (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Mahood, Samuel A. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Maisin, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Maki, Niilo Johannes (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Marjolin, Robert (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Mathias, Ernst E.M. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Melville, James (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mendillo, John Carl Francis (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Meritt, Herbert D. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Messimy, Robert (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Mestre, Harold (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Metraux, Alfred (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mishina, Shoei (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Mitchell, Sydney B. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Mommsen, Theodor Ernst (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Montroll, Elliott Waters (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Moon, Merl P. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Moore, J. Leonard (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Moore, Maurice Louis (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - More, Kenneth Riddell (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Motter, Thomas Hubbard Vail (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Moyer, Laurence Sorver (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Murdoch, David Caruthers (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Nachad, George (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Nagler, Alois M. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Nagy, Elmer (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Newhall, Sidney Merritt (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Nichol, Archibald Jamieson (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Nisoli, Franz Elisee N.E. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Obrador, Alcalde Sixto (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Odlozilik, Otokar (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Ogawa, Teizo (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Olin, John Frank (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Olsen, Karl David (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - O'Meara, William Joseph (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Oppenheimer, Oskar (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Opper, Lincoln (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Orten, James M. (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Owen, David Edward (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Pagan, Francis M. (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Parra, Jose (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Paschall, Dorothy May (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Peacock, Martin Alfred (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Peck, Robert Lawrence (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Pettis, Billy James (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Pfeiffer, Isabelle W. (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Plopper, Clifford Henry (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Porter, Richard William (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Powerdermaker, Hortense (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Raffel, Daniel (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Ralli, Elaine Pandia (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Randels, William Conrad (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Rapp, Franz (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Reid, John Robert (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Reti, Rudolph R. (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Riggs, Douglas Shepard (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Robinson, Robert Anthony (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Romanoff, Pinchas (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Rosahn, Paul Dolin (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Rose, Morris Edgar (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Rosenbaum, Jack Davidson (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Rosenthal, Gerhard (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Ross, Philip (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Rostovtzoff, M.I. (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Rubin, Isidor Clinton (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Russell, Jane Anne (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Saari, Eino Armas (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Sager, Oscar (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Sale, William Merritt, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Salomon, Kurt (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Sands, Lila (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Sarber, Olive May (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Scharrer, Ernst (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Schotte, Oscar (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Seitz, Robert Wilcox (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Semerat, Kazimierz (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sembrat, Zofja (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sharpe, Robert Boies (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sheehan, Donal (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Shelton, Elbert M. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Shepperson, Archibald Bolling (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Shipley, Reginald Alden (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Sifferd, Robert Harris (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Skau, Evald Laurids (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Albert C. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Charles Sieney (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Emil L. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Soderman, Magnus A. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Souders, Mott, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Spohn, Adelaide (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sprunt, Douglas Hamilton (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Starbuck, Helen Lillian (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Stavely, Homer Eaton (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Stodola, Frank Harold (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Street, Harold Richardson (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stukey, Harold Jacob (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Syrjamaki, John (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Szepsenwol, Josel (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Talavera, Pedro J. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Thomas, George Finger (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Thomas, Robert Marrenner (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Tinker, Chauncey B. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Tinklepaugh, Otto Lief (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Toland, John Martin (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Tongue, William Richard (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Town, Bernard William (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Tsai, Burg (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Turner, Francis John (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Turner, Lorenzo Dow (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Valentine, Joseph Munson (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Vernon, Philip E. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Vokes, Harold Ernest (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Von Bodelschwingh, Hans (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Vulcan, Constantin Theodore (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Walker, Arthur Earl (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Weinreich, Max (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Welles, Sherred Belin (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Wheeler, Bernice (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - White, Abraham (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - White, Julius (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Wigderson, Henry (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Williams, William Lane (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Winnek, Philip Stanley (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Winzler, Richard John (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Wolf, Alice (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Woodger, J.H. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Wyss, Oscar Adolf Marcus (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Yoshioka, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Young, Paul Thomas (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Young, William Caldwell (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Zebrowska, Maria (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Zorn, Max August (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Akerlof, Gosta (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Anderson, Anna Margaret (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Armstrong, John Milton, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Aubert, Marcel (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Baker, Noel Philip (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Baur, P.V.C. (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Bellinger, Alfred Raymond (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Benson, Adolph (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Bloomfield, Leonard (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Blum, Robert Isidor (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Boorsch, Jean (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Buck, Peter Henry (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Chao, Yuan Ren (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Cohen, Morris R. (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Coker, Francis William (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Cowgill, George Raymond (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Davie, Maurice R. (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Davis, Jerome (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Devane, William Clyde (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Dietrich, Joseph Robert (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Dollard, John (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Dudley, S.W. (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Dunn, Frederick Sherwood (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Evans-Pritchard, Edward Evans (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Farrell, Michael Anthony (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Feuillerart, Albert G. (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Focillon, Henri (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Fulton, John Farquahar (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Gambrill, Bessie Lee (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Gesell, Arnold (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Greulich, William Walter (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Haberler, Gottfried (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Hahn, Glenn Gardner (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Halsey, Maxwell Nicoll (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Hanley, Miles L. (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Harmon, A.M. (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Harvey, Samuel G. (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Healy, Kent Tenney (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Hendrickson, George Lincoln (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Hille, Einar Carl (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Hoenigswald Heinrich Max Franz (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Holborn, Hajo (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Hutchins, Henry Clinton (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Hutchinson, George Evelyn (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Jahn, Theodore Louis (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Jacobsen, Carlyle F. (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Johnson, Alvin Saunders (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Treat E. (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Kirby, Richard S. (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Knower, Henry McEldery (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Langer, William Leonard (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Laski, Harold J. (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Lowenstein, Karl (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Luquiens, Frederick B. (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - McClintock, Miller (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - McIlwain, Charles Howard (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Malinowski, Bronislaw (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Marquis, Dorothy Postle (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mathevson, C.H. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Matson, Theodore Malvin (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mattusch, Kurt Robert (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Meeks, Everett V. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Mendell, Clarence (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Mitchell, S.K. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Moats, Helen (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Moore, Olive (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Mumford, William Bryant (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Nicholas, J.S. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Oberman, Julian Joel (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Onsager, Lars (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Osborn, James Marshall (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Osgood, Cornelius Berrien (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Page, Leigh (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Petrunkevitch, A. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Rettger, Leo F. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Robinson, Edward S. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Rogers, James Harvey (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Rose, R. Selden (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Rouse, Benjamin Irving, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - St. John, Harold (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Sapir, Eduard (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Schreiber, Carl F. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Schumpeter, Joseph Alois (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Sewall, Richard Benson (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Shedd, Clarence Prouty (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Sheldon, W.H. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Skottsberg, Paul (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Slichter, Sumner H. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Smith, Arthur H. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Spier, Leslie (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Stone, Leon Stansfield (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Strayer, George Dayton (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Thurnwald, C. Richard (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Tilton, John Warren (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Trager, George Leonard (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Truex, Ruth Olmstead (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Urban, W.M. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Vickery, Hubert B. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Warren, Charles H. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Wasserman, Elga Ruth (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Wei, Francis Cho-Min (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Weigand, Herman J. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Welles, Charles Bradford (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Wendt, G. Richard (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Winslow, C.E.A. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Wissler, Clark (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Young, Dana (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Records of Thomas Applequist as dean, circa 1983-2005; Accession 2019-A-0028
  Restricted until January 1, 2081.
  - Administrtive files
    - Admissions
      - 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Admissions data
      - 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Admissions targets, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Association of American Universities, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Centennial celebration, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Coalition for the Advancement of Foreign Language and International Studies, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Commencement
      - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty-annual report, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Course enrollment
      - 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Diversity committee
      - 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dwarves and elves, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Environmental and Health and Safety, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Faculty leaves
      - 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - FLAS Fellowship Awards committee
      - 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Meeting minutes and faculty lists, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Re-admissions
      - 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Department Chair files
    - African Studies, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - African American Studies, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Agrarian Studies, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - American Studies, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Anthropology, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Applied Mathematics, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Archaeology, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Astronomy, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Biology, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Biology-Alice Cheung, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Biomedical Engineering, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Cell Biology, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Cellular and Molecular Physiology, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Chemistry, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Chemistry, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1990-1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Classsics, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Classsics, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Cognitive Science, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Comparative Literature, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Comparative Literature, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Computer Science
      - 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Concilium, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Drama School, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - East Asian Languages and Literature, 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - East Asian Studies, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology
      - 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Economics
      - 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Economic Growth Center, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Engineering and Applied Science, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Engineering and Applied Science, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1992-1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - English
      - 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - 1989-1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - 1990-1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Engineering, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Experimental Medicine, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Research Grant Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Film Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - French, 1990-1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Genetics, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 1990-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - German, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - History
      - 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - 1989-1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - History-current students, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
    - History of Medicine, 1990-1998 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Immunology, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Institute of Biospheric Studies, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Islamic Studies, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - International Relations, 1991-1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Social and Policy Studies, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Italian, 1989-1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Law School, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Linguistics, 1990-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Linguistics, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Luce Fund for Asian Studies, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Management, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Management-Prashant Kapoor, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Mathematics, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Mathematics, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Medical School, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Medical School-PhD programs, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Medieval Studies, 1990-1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry
      - 1992-1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Near East Language and Civilizations, 1992-1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Near East Language and Literature Review Committee, 1990-1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Neuroscience, 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Nursing, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Operations Research, 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Operations Research, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Organizational Behavior, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Organizational Management, 1990-1995 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Pharmacology, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Philosophy
      - 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - 1990-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Physics
      - 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - 1994-1998 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Political Economics-Sylvia Maxfield, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Political Science
      - 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - 1992-1998 (Box 8, Folder 19-20)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Psychology
      - 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Psychology-Clinical Psychology, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Religious Studies, 1992-1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)